Today mom did my hairstyle and
what did I do to mom?  So for quite some
time now we are running out of wash basin in our bathroom
because the old one has
passed away.  And mom and dad are saying that you
never forget to eat momos.  She
always forgets to bring the wash basin.  That's why I am thinking of getting it
today because my family members have taken a
vow that they will take bath only
when the wash basin is available.  Hey, no problem,
I will take bath as everyone's share.  Now after taking
bath he said to his mother, O Mother, please
do my hair today.  Like I used to make during school time,
mom made these two braids.
Then I also made mom's
hairstyle and styled these two braids
with a cap.  I am looking like a berry.  Now let us
leave for the market
in our vehicle.  But after coming to the market I found
out that the entire market was closed today.
With great difficulty I found a shop and even here
only three options were available.  So I
liked this one.  I also took a shower while I was at it.
Then she threw this wash basin in the car
and came straight to buy pots.  Because if
these pots are not taken home today, my mother will send me straight to my
in-laws' house.  Why Doremi?  I
also bought a piggy bank with Doremi on it.  I have to save some
small change for the wedding.